Harvard College Observatory observations, logs, instrument readings, and calculations: an inventory
Harvard College Observatory observations, logs, instrument readings, and calculations
- Comets, 1892 to 1899; KG11365.515 (Box 15)
- Parallax Computations #2; Comets, 1891 to 1893; KG11365.516 (Box 15)
- Comets and Variable Star observations, 1892; KG11365.517 (Box 15)
- Comets, 1892 to 1897; KG11365.518 (Box 15)
- [Observations] 66, 1892 to 1893; KG11365.519 (Box 15)
- [Observations] 67, 1893; KG11365.520 (Box 15)
- [Observations] 68, 1893 to 1894; KG11365.521 (Box 15)
- [Observations] 69, 1894; KG11365.522 (Box 15)
- [Observations] 70, 1894; KG11365.523 (Box 16)
- [Observations] 72, 1894; KG11365.524 (Box 16)
- Journal (Cambridge) #3, 1893 to 1895; KG11365.525 (Box 16)
- Variable Stars, 1894 to 1895; KG11365.526 (Box 16)
  William B. Clymer.
- [Observations] 73, 1894 to 1894; KG11365.527 (Box 16)
- [Observations] 76, 1895; KG11365.528 (Box 16)
- Variable Stars 6-inch west equatorial, 1895 to 1898; KG11365.529 (Box 16)
- [Observations] 77, 1895; KG11365.530 (Box 16)
- [Observations] 79, 1896; KG11365.531 (Box 16)
- [Observations] 80, 1896; KG11365.532 (Box 16)
- [Observations] 81, 1896; KG11365.533 (Box 16)
- Variable Stars (Arequipa), 1895 to 1898; KG11365.534 (Box 16)
- [Observations], 1895 to 1898; KG11365.535 (Box 16)
  Annie J. Cannon.
- [Observations] 85, 1896; KG11365.536 (Box 16)
- Variable Stars, 1895 to 1899; KG11365.537 (Box 16)
- Telescope Mechanical Notes and Golf Scores, 1897 to 1911; KG11365.538 (Box 16)
  Charles P. Howard.
- [Observations] 94, 1897 to 1898; KG11365.539 (Box 16)
- [Observations], 1898 to 1900; KG11365.540 (Box 16)
- Variable Stars, 1899; KG11365.541 (Box 16)
- Variable Star Observations, 1899; KG11365.542 (Box 16)
  Solon Irving Bailey.
- Variable Star Observations, 1899 to 1902; KG11365.543 (Box 16)
- [Observations], 1900 to 1901; KG11365.544 (Box 16)
- [Observations], 1901; KG11365.545 (Box 17)
  Also identified as: 122.
  See KG11366.371 and preceeding for earlier volumes in sequence.
- [Observations], 1901; KG11365.546 (Box 17)
  Also identified as: 123.
- Notebook #2, 1902 to 1905; KG11365.547 (Box 17)
- [Observations], 1901 to 1905; KG11365.548 (Box 17)
  See KG11366.374 and KG11366.375.
- [Observations], 1901; KG11365.549 (Box 17)
  Also identified as: 126.
- [Observations], 1901; KG11365.550 (Box 17)
  Also identified as: 127.
- [Observations], 1901; KG11365.551 (Box 17)
  Also identified as: [128].
- [Observations], 1901 to 1902; KG11365.552 (Box 17)
  Also identified as: 129.
- [Observations], 1902; KG11365.553 (Box 17)
  Also identified as: 130.
- [Observations], 1902; KG11365.554 (Box 17)
  Also identified as: 131.
- [Observations], 1902; KG11365.555 (Box 17)
  Also identified as: 132.
- [Observations], 1902; KG11365.556 (Box 17)
  Also identified as: 133.
- [Observations], 1902; KG11365.557 (Box 17)
  Also identified as: 134.
- [Observations], 1902 to 1903; KG11365.558 (Box 17)
  Also identified as: 135.
- [Observations], 1903; KG11365.559 (Box 17)
  Also identified as: 136.
- [Observations], 1903; KG11365.560 (Box 17)
  Also identified as: 137.
- [Observations], 1903; KG11365.561 (Box 17)
  Also identified as: 138.
- [Observations], 1903; KG11365.562 (Box 17)
  Also identified as: 139.
- [Observations], 1903; KG11365.563 (Box 17)
  Also identified as: 140.
- [Observations], 1903; KG11365.564 (Box 17)
  Also identified as: 141.
- [Observations], 1903 to 1904; KG11365.565 (Box 18)
  Also identified as: 142.
- [Observations], 1904; KG11365.566 (Box 18)
  Also identified as: 143.
- [Observations], 1904; KG11365.567 (Box 18)
  Also identified as: 144.
- [Observations], 1904; KG11365.568 (Box 18)
  Also identified as: 145.
- [Observations], 1904; KG11365.569 (Box 18)
  Also identified as: 146.
- [Observations], 1904; KG11365.570 (Box 18)
  Also identified as: 147.
- [Observations], 1904; KG11365.571 (Box 18)
  Also identified as: 148.
- [Observations], 1904 to 1905; KG11365.572 (Box 18)
  Also identified as: 149.
- [Observations], 1905; KG11365.573 (Box 18)
  Also identified as: 150.
- [Observations], 1905; KG11365.574 (Box 18)
  Also identified as: 151.
- [Observations], 1905; KG11365.575 (Box 18)
  Also identified as: 152.
- [Observations], 1905; KG11365.576 (Box 18)
  Also identified as: 153.
- [Observations], 1905 to 1906; KG11365.577 (Box 18)
  Also identified as: 154.
- [Observations], 1906; KG11365.578 (Box 18)
  Also identified as: 155.
- [Observations], 1906; KG11365.579 (Box 18)
  Also identified as: 156.
- [Observations], 1906; KG11365.580 (Box 18)
  Also identified as: 157.
- [Observations], 1906; KG11365.581 (Box 18)
  Also identified as: 158.
- [Observations], 1906 to 1907; KG11365.582 (Box 18)
  Also identified as: 159.
- [Observations], 1907; KG11365.583 (Box 18)
  Also identified as: 160.
- [Observations], 1907; KG11365.584 (Box 18)
  Also identified as: 161.
- [Observations], 1907; KG11365.585 (Box 18)
  Also identified as: 162.
- [Observations], 1907; KG11365.586 (Box 19)
  Also identified as: 163.
- [Observations], 1907 to 1908; KG11365.587 (Box 19)
  Also identified as: 164.
- [Observations], 1908; KG11365.588 (Box 19)
  Also identified as: 165.
- [Observations], 1908; KG11365.589 (Box 19)
  Also identified as: 166.
- [Observations], 1908; KG11365.590 (Box 19)
  Also identified as: 167.
- [Observations], 1908; KG11365.591 (Box 19)
  Also identified as: 168.
- [Observations], 1908; KG11365.592 (Box 19)
  Also identified as: 169.
- [Observations], 1908 to 1909; KG11365.593 (Box 19)
  Also identified as: 170.
- [Observations], 1909; KG11365.594 (Box 19)
  Also identified as: 171.
- [Observations], 1909; KG11365.595 (Box 19)
  Also identified as: 172.
- [Observations], 1909; KG11365.596 (Box 19)
  Also identified as: 173.
- [Observations], 1909; KG11365.597 (Box 19)
  Also identified as: 174.
- [Observations], 1909; KG11365.598 (Box 19)
  Also identified as: 175.
- [Observations], 1909 to 1910; KG11365.599 (Box 19)
  Also identified as: 176.
- [Observations], 1910; KG11365.600 (Box 19)
  Also identified as: 177.
- [Observations], 1910; KG11365.601 (Box 19)
  Also identified as: 178.
- [Observations], 1910; KG11365.602 (Box 19)
  Also identified as: 179.
- [Observations], 1910 to 1911; KG11365.603 (Box 19)
  Also identified as: 180.
- [Observations], 1911; KG11365.604 (Box 19)
  Also identified as: 181.
- [Observations], 1911; KG11365.605 (Box 19)
  Also identified as: 182.
- [Observations], 1911; KG11365.606 (Box 19)
  Also identified as: 183.
- [Observations], 1911 to 1912; KG11365.607 (Box 19)
  Also identified as: 184.
- [Observations], 1912; KG11365.608 (Box 20)
  Also identified as: 185.
- [Observations], 1912; KG11365.609 (Box 20)
  Also identified as: 186.
- [Observations], 1912; KG11365.610 (Box 20)
  Also identified as: 187.
- 15-inch Record, 1912 to 1913; KG11365.611 (Box 20)
- [Observations], 1912 to 1915; KG11365.612 (Box 20)
  Also identified as: 188.
- [Observations], 1915 to 1916; KG11365.613 (Box 20)
  Also identified as: 189.
- [Observations], 1916; KG11365.614 (Box 20)
  Also identified as: 190.
- [Observations], 1916; KG11365.615 (Box 20)
  Also identified as: 191.
- [Observations], 1916; KG11365.616 (Box 20)
  Also identified as: 192.
- [Observations], 1916; KG11365.617 (Box 20)
  Also identified as: 193.
- [Observations], 1916 to 1917; KG11365.618 (Box 20)
  Also identified as: 194.
- [Observations], 1917; KG11365.619 (Box 20)
  Also identified as: 195.
- [Observations], 1917; KG11365.620 (Box 20)
  Also identified as: 196.
- 15-inch Equatorial, 1917; KG11365.621 (Box 20)
  Also identified as: 197.
- 15-inch Equatorial, 1917; KG11365.622 (Box 20)
  Also identified as: 198.
- 15-inch Equatorial, 1917 to 1918; KG11365.623 (Box 20)
  Also identified as: 199.
- 15-inch Equatorial, 1918; KG11365.624 (Box 20)
  Also identified as: 200.
- 15-inch Equatorial, 1918; KG11365.625 (Box 20)
  Also identified as: 201.
- 15-inch Equatorial, 1918 to 1919; KG11365.626 (Box 20)
  Also identified as: 202.
- 15-inch Equatorial, 1919 to 1920; KG11365.627 (Box 20)
  Also identified as: 203.
- 15-inch Equatorial, 1920 to 1923; KG11365.628 (Box 21)
  Also identified as: 204.
- 15-inch Equatorial, 1926 to 1927; KG11365.629 (Box 21)
  Also identified as: 205.
- 15-inch Equatorial, 1928 to 1930; KG11365.630 (Box 21)
  Also identified as: 206.
- 15-inch Equatorial, 1934 to 1935; KG11365.631 (Box 21)
  Also identified as: 207.
- 15-inch Equatorial, 1935 to 1936; KG11365.632 (Box 21)
  Also identified as: 208.
- 15-inch Equatorial, 1936; KG11365.633 (Box 21)
  Also identified as: 209.
- 15-inch Equatorial, 1936; KG11365.634 (Box 21)
  Also identified as: 210.
- 15-inch Equatorial, 1936 to 1939; KG11365.635 (Box 21)
  Also identified as: 211.
- 15-inch Equatorial, 1936 to 1937; KG11365.636 (Box 21)
  Also identified as: 212.
- 12-inch Equatorial, 1914; KG11365.637 (Box 21)
  Also identified as: 1.
- 12-inch Equatorial, 1915 to 1916; KG11365.638 (Box 21)
- 12-inch Equatorial, 1916 to 1917; KG11365.639 (Box 21)
- 12-inch Equatorial (Observations from Arequipa), 1917 to 1918; KG11365.640 (Box 21)
- 12-inch Equatorial, 1919; KG11365.641 (Box 21)
- [Box of Papers] II Meteors (Leonids), 1898 to 1899; KG11365.642 (Box 21)
- 12-inch Equatorial - Variable Star Observations, 1919 to 1920; KG11365.643 (Box 22)
- 12-inch Equatorial - Variable Star Observations, 1920; KG11365.644 (Box 22)
- 12-inch Equatorial - Variable Star Observations, 1920 to 1921; KG11365.645 (Box 22)
- 12-inch Equatorial - Variable Star Observations, 1921; KG11365.646 (Box 22)
- 12-inch Equatorial - Variable Star Observations, 1921; KG11365.647 (Box 22)
- 12-inch Equatorial - Variable Star Observations, 1921; KG11365.648 (Box 22)
- 12-inch Equatorial - Variable Star Observations, 1921 to 1922; KG11365.649 (Box 22)
- 12-inch Equatorial - Variable Star Observations, 1922; KG11365.650 (Box 22)
- 12-inch Equatorial - Variable Star Observations, 1922; KG11365.651 (Box 22)
- 12-inch Equatorial - Variable Star Observations, 1922 to 1923; KG11365.652 (Box 22)
- 12-inch Equatorial - Variable Star Observations, 1923; KG11365.653 (Box 22)
- 12-inch Equatorial - Variable Star Observations, 1923; KG11365.654 (Box 22)
- 12-inch Equatorial - Variable Star Observations, 1923 to 1924; KG11365.655 (Box 22)
- 12-inch Equatorial - Variable Star Observations, 1924; KG11365.656 (Box 22)
- 12-inch Equatorial - Variable Star Observations, 1924 to 1925; KG11365.657 (Box 22)
- 12-inch Equatorial - Variable Star Observations, 1925; KG11365.658 (Box 22)
- 12-inch Equatorial - Variable Star Observations, 1925 to 1926; KG11365.659 (Box 22)
- 12-inch Equatorial - Variable Star Observations, 1925 to 1926; KG11365.660 (Box 22)
- 12-inch Equatorial - Variable Star Observations, 1926 to 1927; KG11365.661 (Box 22)
- 12-inch Equatorial - Variable Star Observations, 1927; KG11365.662 (Box 22)
- 12-inch Equatorial - Variable Star Observations, 1927 to 1928; KG11365.663 (Box 23)
- 12-inch Equatorial - Variable Star Observations, 1928 to 1929; KG11365.664 (Box 23)
- 12-inch Equatorial - Variable Star Observations, 1928 to 1933; KG11365.665 (Box 23)
- 12-inch Equatorial - Variable Star Observations, 1934 to 1935; KG11365.666 (Box 23)
- 12-inch Equatorial - Variable Star Observations, 1935 to 1936; KG11365.667 (Box 23)
- [24-inch Clark Refractor], 1905 to 1906; KG11365.668 (Box 23)
  Leon Campbell.
- [24-inch Clark Refractor], 1907; KG11365.669 (Box 23)
  Also identified as: 3.
  See KG11365.758 for volume 2.
- [24-inch Clark Refractor], 1907 to 1908; KG11365.670 (Box 23)
  Also identified as: 4.
- [24-inch Clark Refractor], 1908 to 1909; KG11365.671 (Box 23)
  Also identified as: 5.
- [24-inch Clark Refractor], 1909; KG11365.672 (Box 23)
  Also identified as: 6.
- [24-inch Clark Refractor], 1909; KG11365.673 (Box 23)
  Also identified as: 7.
- [24-inch Clark Refractor], 1909 to 1910; KG11365.674 (Box 23)
  Also identified as: 8.
- [24-inch Clark Refractor], 1910 to 1911; KG11365.675 (Box 23)
  Also identified as: 9.
- Photometric Observations, 1872; KG11365.676 (Box 23)
- Photometric Observations, 1872; KG11365.677 (Box 23)
  Also identified as: 2.
- Photometric Observations, 1872; KG11365.678 (Box 23)
- Photometric Observations, 1873; KG11365.679 (Box 23)
- Photometric Observations, 1873; KG11365.680 (Box 23)
- Photometric Observations, 1874; KG11365.681 (Box 23)
- Photometric Observations, 1874; KG11365.682 (Box 23)
- Photometric Observations, 1874 to 1875; KG11365.683 (Box 23)
- Experiments with Photometer, 1872; KG11365.684 (Box 23)
- Eta Centauri Spectral Study, 1911; KG11365.685 (Box 23)
  Leah B. Allen.
- Clusters - spectrophotmetric tracings, 1930; KG11365.686 (Box 23)
  Carol Jane Anger.
- Spectrophotometric tracings (Alpha Cyg, Vega), 1930 to 1936; KG11365.687 (Box 23)
- Spectrophotometric tracings (Alpha Cyg, Vega), 1930 to 1936; KG11365.688 (Box 23)
- Eta Per, NGC 663 - spectrophotmetric tracings, KG11365.689 (Box 24)
- Clusters - spectrophotmetric tracings, 1932; KG11365.690 (Box 24)
- Clusters - spectrophotmetric tracings, 1934; KG11365.691 (Box 24)
- Miscellaneous; Variables, 1918 to 1919; KG11365.692 (Box 24)
  Mary D. Applegate.
- Variables, Map of the Sky, 1918 to 1919; KG11365.693 (Box 24)
- Map of the Sky, Sequences for Orion Nebula, 1919; KG11365.694 (Box 24)
- Asteroids and Novae, 1919 to 1920; KG11365.695 (Box 24)
- Novae and Variables, 1920 to 1921; KG11365.696 (Box 24)
- Map of the Sky, 1920 to 1921; KG11365.697 (Box 24)
- Daily Journal [13-inch - Peru], 1889 to 1890; KG11365.698 (Box 24)
- Double Stars; Planets (13-inch - Peru), 1894 to 1896; KG11365.699 (Box 24)
  Also identified as: 25.
- Miscellaneous; Variables, 1917 to 1919; KG11365.700 (Box 24)
  Dorothy W. Block.
- Spectrum Work, 1917 to 1919; KG11365.701 (Box 24)
- Omicron Ceti, Nova Aql 3, 1917 to 1919; KG11365.702 (Box 24)
- Variables, 1918 to 1919; KG11365.703 (Box 24)
- Asteroids, 1918 to 1919; KG11365.704 (Box 24)
- Variables, 1919; KG11365.705 (Box 24)
- Variable Stars and Meteors, 1903; KG11365.706 (Box 24)
  F.E. Brasch.
- Variable Stars, 1896 to 1898; KG11365.707 (Box 24)
  Sarah E. Breslin.
- Variable Stars, 1898; KG11365.708 (Box 24)
- Variable Stars, 1898; KG11365.709 (Box 25)
- Variable Stars, 1899; KG11365.710 (Box 25)
- Variable Stars, 1901 to 1902; KG11365.711 (Box 25)
- Variable Stars, 1902; KG11365.712 (Box 25)
- Variable Stars, 1902 to 1903; KG11365.713 (Box 25)
- Variable Stars, 1903; KG11365.714 (Box 25)
- Variable Stars, 1903; KG11365.715 (Box 25)
- Variable Stars, 1903; KG11365.716 (Box 25)
  Also identified as: 10.
- Variable Stars, 1903; KG11365.717 (Box 25)
  Also identified as: 11.
- Variable Stars, 1903 to 1904; KG11365.718 (Box 25)
  Also identified as: 12.
- Variable Stars, 1904; KG11365.719 (Box 25)
  Also identified as: 13.
- Variable Stars, 1904; KG11365.720 (Box 25)
  Also identified as: 14.
- Variable Stars, 1904; KG11365.721 (Box 25)
  Also identified as: 15.
- Variable Stars, 1904; KG11365.722 (Box 25)
  Also identified as: 16.
- Variable Stars, 1904; KG11365.723 (Box 25)
  Also identified as: 17.
- Variable Stars, 1904 to 1905; KG11365.724 (Box 25)
  Also identified as: 18.
- Variable Stars, 1905; KG11365.725 (Box 25)
  Also identified as: 19.
- Variable Stars, 1905; KG11365.726 (Box 25)
  Also identified as: 20.
- Variable Stars, 1905 to 1906; KG11365.727 (Box 25)
  Also identified as: 21.
- Variable Stars, 1906; KG11365.728 (Box 25)
  Also identified as: 22.
- Variable Stars, 1906; KG11365.729 (Box 26)
  Also identified as: 23.
- Variable Stars, 1906; KG11365.730 (Box 26)
  Also identified as: 24.
- Variable Stars, 1906; KG11365.731 (Box 26)
- Variable Stars, 1906; KG11365.732 (Box 26)
  Also identified as: 26.
- Variable Stars, 1907; KG11365.733 (Box 26)
  Also identified as: 27.
- Variable Stars, 1907; KG11365.734 (Box 26)
  Also identified as: 28.
- Variable Stars, 1907; KG11365.735 (Box 26)
  Also identified as: 29.
- Variable Stars, 1907 to 1908; KG11365.736 (Box 26)
  Also identified as: 30.
- Variable Stars, 1908; KG11365.737 (Box 26)
  Also identified as: [31].
- Variable Stars, 1908; KG11365.738 (Box 26)
  Also identified as: 32.
- Variable Stars, 1909; KG11365.739 (Box 26)
  Also identified as: 33.
- Variable Stars, 1909 to 1910; KG11365.740 (Box 26)
  Also identified as: 34.
- Variable Stars, 1910 to 1911; KG11365.741 (Box 26)
  Also identified as: 35.
- Magnitude Estimates, 1903; KG11365.742 (Box 26)
  Also identified as: [4].
- Comparison Stars for Variables, 1922; KG11365.743 (Box 26)
  L.A. Brigham.
- Variable Stars, 1919; KG11365.744 (Box 26)
  Grace R. Brooks.
- Variable Stars, 1901 to 1902; KG11365.745 (Box 26)
- Variable Stars, 1902 to 1903; KG11365.746 (Box 26)
- Variable Stars, 1903; KG11365.747 (Box 26)
- Variable Stars, 1903 to 1904; KG11365.748 (Box 26)
- Variable Stars, 1904; KG11365.749 (Box 27)
- Variable Stars, 1904 to 1905; KG11365.750 (Box 27)
- Variable Stars, 1905 to 1907; KG11365.751 (Box 27)
- Variable Stars, 1907 to 1908; KG11365.752 (Box 27)
- Variable Stars, 1908 to 1909; KG11365.753 (Box 27)
- Variable Stars, 1909 to 1911; KG11365.754 (Box 27)
- Observations with Photographs X on 5-inch, 1903 to 1906; KG11365.755 (Box 27)
- Observations with Photographs X on 5-inch, 1903 to 1905; KG11365.756 (Box 27)
- Observations with Photographs X on 5-inch, 1905; KG11365.757 (Box 27)
  K.L. identity uncertain.
- Observations with Photographs X on 5-inch, 1906 to 1907; KG11365.758 (Box 27)
- Photometric Observations, 1915; KG11365.759 (Box 27)
- 6-inch (west) Equatorial, 1917 to 1924; KG11365.760 (Box 27)
- Memoranda on Variable Stars, 1904 to 1905; KG11365.761 (Box 27)
- 8-inch Polar Telescope, 1908 to 1909; KG11365.762 (Box 27)
- 8-inch Polar Telescope, 1909 to 1911; KG11365.763 (Box 27)
- Variable Star Observations, 1911 to 1912; KG11365.764 (Box 27)
- Variable Star Observations, 1912 to 1914; KG11365.765 (Box 27)
- S I 8 17, 1911 to 1912; KG11365.766 (Box 27)
- Photometric Records, 1913 to 1915; KG11365.767 (Box 27)
- Variable Star Observations, 1914 to 1915; KG11365.768 (Box 28)
- Log Book - Arequipa Station of HCO, 1915; KG11365.769 (Box 28)
- P #17, 1913; KG11365.770 (Box 28)
- Pyrheliometer 17 Observation, 1914; KG11365.771 (Box 28)
- Estimate of Work (Arequipa), 1911; KG11365.772 (Box 28)
- Long Period Southern Variables, 1910; KG11365.773 (Box 28)
- Variables, 1907 to 1909; KG11365.774 (Box 28)
  E.S. Manson and H.E. Blackett, K. L..
- Long Period Southern Variables, 1904 to 1908; KG11365.775 (Box 28)
- Long Period Southern Variables, 1918; KG11365.776 (Box 28)
- Nova Aquilae No. 3, 1918; KG11365.777 (Box 28)
- [Untitled], KG11365.778
  See also KG11366.875.
- Variable Star Observations, 1900 to 1901; KG11365.779 (Box 28)
  Also identified as: [I?].
- Visual observations, 1901 to 1902; KG11365.780 (Box 28)
- Visual observations, 1902 to 1903; KG11365.781 (Box 28)
- Visual observations, 1903 to 1904; KG11365.782 (Box 28)
- Visual observations, 1904; KG11365.783 (Box 28)
- Visual observations, 1904 to 1905; KG11365.784 (Box 28)
- Visual observations, 1905 to 1906; KG11365.785 (Box 28)
- Visual observations, 1906 to 1907; KG11365.786 (Box 28)
  Also identified as: X.
- Visual observations, 1907 to 1909; KG11365.787 (Box 28)
  Also identified as: XI.
- Notes for Reading, 1911 to 1939; KG11365.788 (Box 28)
  Also identified as: 101.
- Guest Book, 1912 to 1935; KG11365.789 (Box 28)
- Variable Stars, Longitude Determination, 1862 to 1882; KG11365.790 (Box 29)
  Seth C. Chandler.
- Variable Stars, Longitude Determination, KG11365.791 (Box 29)
  Stored under KG11366.1080.
- W. Virginis I, 1916; KG11365.792 (Box 29)
  C.A. Chant.
- Lambda of spectra lines in red region of stars, 1926 to 1927; KG11365.793 (Box 29)
  C.T. Chase.
- Spectra of Novae, 1926; KG11365.794 (Box 29)
  Also identified as: PD 1.
  Paul Daidovich.
- [Measurements], 1926; KG11365.795 (Box 29)
  Also identified as: PD 2.
- Journal - Latitude And Longitude Work, 1896; KG11365.796 (Box 29)
  Also identified as: [72].
- Radiometric Book I, 1937 to 1938; KG11365.797 (Box 29)
- Radiometry II, 1939 to 1940; KG11365.798 (Box 29)
  E.M. Berson.
- Radiometry Program Book I, 1936 to 1938; KG11365.799 (Box 29)
- Galvanometry Book I, 1937 to 1938; KG11365.800 (Box 29)
- Variable Stars, 1890 to 1892; KG11365.801 (Box 29)
  Williamina P. Fleming.
- Variable Stars, 1892 to 1894; KG11365.802 (Box 29)
- Variable Stars; Spectra, 1892 to 1894; KG11365.803 (Box 29)
- Variable Stars, 1893 to 1898; KG11365.804 (Box 29)
- Variable Stars, 1894 to 1895; KG11365.805 (Box 29)
- Variable Stars; Spectra, 1895 to 1899; KG11365.806 (Box 29)
- Variable Stars, 1895 to 1896; KG11365.807 (Box 29)
- Variable Stars, 1896; KG11365.808 (Box 29)
- Variable Stars, 1896 to 1897; KG11365.809 (Box 29)
- Variable Stars, 1897 to 1898; KG11365.810 (Box 30)
- Variable Stars, 1897 to 1902; KG11365.811 (Box 30)
- Variable Stars, 1898 to 1903; KG11365.812 (Box 30)
- Variable Stars, 1898 to 1905; KG11365.813 (Box 30)
- Variable Stars, 1899 to 1905; KG11365.814 (Box 30)
- Variable Stars; Computations of Spectra, 1903 to 1907; KG11365.815 (Box 30)
- Variable Stars; Computations of Spectra, 1903 to 1910; KG11365.816 (Box 30)
- Variable Stars; Photometer, 1905 to 1908; KG11365.817 (Box 30)
- Novae, Comets, Spectra, 1906 to 1911; KG11365.818 (Box 30)
- Spectral Classification; Miscellaneous Observations, 1908 to 1911; KG11365.819 (Box 30)
- Ledger of LPV's 000339-095659, KG11365.820 (Box 30)
- Ledger of LPV's 100661-185905, KG11365.821 (Box 30)
- Ledger of LPV's 190048-235939, KG11365.822 (Box 30)
- Clusters and Faint Stars, 1904 to 1911; KG11365.823 (Box 30)
- Nova Persei Reductions, 1902; KG11365.824 (Box 30)
- Variable Stars, KG11365.825 (Box 30)
- Measurements of Bright Line Spectra, 1890; KG11365.826 (Box 30)
  Missing 11/1991 (?).
- Reductions of Photographic Observations, KG11365.827 (Box 30)
- Reductions of Photographic Observations, 1886 to 1887; KG11365.828 (Box 30)
- Reductions of Photographic Observations, 1886; KG11365.829 (Box 30)
- Reductions of Photographic Observations, 1886; KG11365.830 (Box 31)
- Reductions of Photographic Observations, 1886 to 1887; KG11365.831 (Box 31)
- Reductions of Photographic Observations, KG11365.832 (Box 31)
- Reductions of Photographic Observations, 1886 to 1887; KG11365.833 (Box 31)
- Reductions of Photographic Observations, 1886 to 1887; KG11365.834 (Box 31)
- Reductions of Photographic Observations, 1887; KG11365.835 (Box 31)
- Reductions of Photographic Observations, 1887; KG11365.836 (Box 31)
- Reductions of Photographic Observations, 1887; KG11365.837 (Box 31)
- Reductions of Photographic Observations, KG11365.838 (Box 31)
- Reductions of Photographic Observations, 1887; KG11365.839 (Box 31)
- Reductions of Photographic Observations, 1887; KG11365.840 (Box 31)
- Reductions of Photographic Observations, 1887; KG11365.841 (Box 31)
- Reductions of Photographic Observations, 1887 to 1888; KG11365.842 (Box 31)
- Reductions of Photographic Observations, 1887; KG11365.843 (Box 31)
- Reductions of Photographic Observations, 1887 to 1889; KG11365.844 (Box 31)
- Reductions of Photographic Observations, KG11365.845 (Box 31)
- Catalog of E. Stars, KG11365.846 (Box 31)
- Description of Spectra, 1887 to 1888; KG11365.847 (Box 31)
- Description of Spectra, 1887 to 1889; KG11365.848 (Box 31)
- Catalog of E. Stars, KG11365.849 (Box 32)
- Catalog of E. Stars, KG11365.850 (Box 32)
- Discordant Spectra; Remarks on Rejected Measures, KG11365.851 (Box 32)
- G Standard Stars on Spectrum Plates, KG11365.852 (Box 32)
- E Standard Stars on Spectrum Plates, KG11365.853 (Box 32)
- Description of Spectra, KG11365.854 (Box 32)
- G Standard Stars on Spectrum Plates, KG11365.855 (Box 32)
  Also identified as: 31.
- Description of Spectra, KG11365.856 (Box 32)
- C Standard Stars on Spectrum Plates, KG11365.857 (Box 32)
- Catalog of I Plates, KG11365.858 (Box 32)
- Reductions of Photographic Observations, KG11365.859 (Box 32)
- F + G Discordant Spectra, KG11365.860 (Box 32)